The Hudson River Environmental Society Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 10. Scenic Hudson Files, 10; 4.33 linear feet 22 - 26 888 - 1144
  - Negatives, 10.3
    - Scenic Hudson – Negatives, Box 25; 10.3
      - Special Events: Indian Hill Loop Trail Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 1077 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Indian Hill Loop Trail; Land Preservation: National Trails Day, 1078 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Irvington Groundmending Ceremony, 1079 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Lighthouse Park, 1080 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Lighthouse Park, Winter Warm Up, 1081 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Mt. Beacon Trailmasters Event, 1082 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Mystery Point Boat Tour, 1083 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: National Trails Day 1993, 1084 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Pancake Breakfast 1994, 1085 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Pancake Breakfast - Linwood, 1086 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Poets’ Walk 1994, 1087 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Poets’ Walk 1997, 1088 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Poets’ Walk Festival 1998, 1089 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Poets’ Walk Park - Chestnut Tree Planting, 1090 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Preservation Hike and Picnic, 1091 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Protest, 1092 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Quitters (?) Reception, 1093 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Rams Horn Opening, 1094 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: River Champion Reception 1992, 1095 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: River Champ Reception 1997, 1096 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: River Champion Reception at Mystery Point, 1097 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Sleightsburgh Park Dedication, 1098 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Sterling Forest Press Conference, 1099 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Regatta 1991, 1100 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Regatta, 1101 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Retreat (staff) 1999, 1102 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Spirit of the River Gala, 1103 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Washington with Clinton, 1104 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Winter Warm Up, 1105 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: (the) Young Friends of Scenic Hudson Autumn Celebration, 1106 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Young Friends - Storm King Mountain, 1107 (Box 25)
      - Special Events: Young Friends Storm King Mountain Hike, 1108 (Box 25)
      - Special Negatives: Used for Publications and Framing, 1109 (Box 25)
      - Specific Municipalities: Kingston Waterfront, 1110 (Box 25)
      - Specific Municipalities: Newburgh, 1111 (Box 25)
      - Specific Municipalities: Poughkeepsie, Kingston, 1112 (Box 25)
      - Specific Municipalities: View of Poughkeepsie from North of Poughkeepsie Bridge, 1113 (Box 25)
      - Turtle, 1114 (Box 25)
      - West Point, Scarborough R. R., 1115 (Box 25)
      - Yonkers Waterfront, 1116 (Box 25)
      - Poets’ Walk Festival (large), 1117 (Box 25)
      - From Adrianee Library, Poughkeepsie (large), 1118 (Box 25)
      - Regatta (large), 1119 (Box 25)
      - From Ruth & William Diebold Collection (large), 1120 (Box 25)
  - Photographs, 10.4
    - Scenic Hudson Photographs, Box 26; 10.4
      Scenic Hudson Photographs
      - Education: Environmental: Animal Tracking, 1121 (Box 26)
      - Education: Third Grade Class at Shaupeneak Ridge, 1122 (Box 26)
      - Fishing, 1123 (Box 26)
      - Historic Plaques, 1124 (Box 26)
      - Land Preservation: Clausland Mountain, 1125 (Box 26)
      - Land Preservation: Fishkill Ridge, 1126 (Box 26)
      - Land Preservation: Foundry Cove, 1127 (Box 26)
      - Land Preservation: Four Mile Point, 1128 (Box 26)
      - Land Preservation: Shaupeneak Ridge Dedication, 1129 (Box 26)
      - Land Preservation: West Point Foundry Preserve, 1130 (Box 26)
      - Mounted Colored Pics: Storm King (1), 1131 (Box 26)
      - Mounted Colored Pics: Storm King (2), 1132 (Box 26)
      - Mounted Colored Pics: Storm King (3), 1133 (Box 26)
      - People: Untitled, 1134 (Box 26)
      - Special Events: Brownfields Project - Irvington, 1135 (Box 26)
      - Special Events: Dia Hard Hat Tor (also negatives), 1136 (Box 26)
      - Special Events: (the) Great River Sweep 2000, 1137 (Box 26)
      - Special Events: (the) Great River Sweep (also negatives), 1138 (Box 26)
      - Special Events: Poets’ Walk Festival (also negatives), 1139 (Box 26)
      - Special Events: Winter Warm Up - Madam Brett Park, 1140 (Box 26)
      - Specific Municipalities: Poughkeepsie Waterfront (also negatives), 1141 (Box 26)
      - Specific Municipalities: Yonkers Waterfront Press Conference, 1142 (Box 26)
      - Landscapes (large), 1143 (Box 26)
      - Photos by Robert Beckhard (large), 1144 (Box 26)
- 11. HRES History/Background, 11; 0.33 linear feet 26 1145 - 1153
  Historical documents, financial papers, and membership information of the Hudson River Environmental Society.
  - Historical Documents, 11.1
    - Historical Documents, Box 26; 11.1
      Charter and purpose of HRES
      - Charter, 1145 (Box 26)
      - Charter, 1146 (Box 26)
      - Statement of Purpose, 1147 (Box 26)
  - Financial Documents, 11.2
    - Financial Papers, Box 26; 11.2
      HRES financial transactions and correspondence
      - Grant Proposal, 01/09/1980, 1148 (Box 26)
      - Funding Correspondence, 1149 (Box 26)
      - Record of Transactions, 1150 (Box 26)
  - Biographical Materials, 11.3
  - Biographical Materials, Box 26; 11.3
    Background information on HRES members
    - Biographical data, 1151 (Box 26)
    - Biography of Hofman, Peter, 1152 (Box 26)
    - Membership Information, 1153 (Box 26)